A high-rise with shares and welcome back again
today we will talk about ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited
is the last stock company in the year 2008 whose market capital
is more than sixty five thousand crores if we
talk about the middle then it is 0.24 percent which is very
low if we talk about the industries sector then it is
available at 32.4 percent which is four point 618
price to place of the company is 9.17 and its
share on Anil is 32.40 if we
look at its previous graph see this is the previous
graph
that St. Louis has shown a lock at 1.85
whichever is higher and the application is running it is
running at 42037 if we look at its one week
graph then it has almost reached the
office yesterday in this it has given two highest votes in one week that is it
if we
check its fiber graph then
see here it has shown a lock of 100  12.49 versus
generator has been given, the high it had set in the last five years was
z6
and its districts were very low, in fact,
they are more opposite from 1628, if we
talk about its status, if we look at the file special
train, their revenue has
grown from 2018 to 221, it has grown from one point 48 to
12.68, their revenue
accountant has shown here, when we
talk about profit, then the profit has increased without any increase,
0.86
1.4 of Seth, here we can see
how much the gang is active in both profit and revenue,
so from their fundamentals they
look very strong, here if
we talk about share holding pattern, then
promoters holding is given the highest here,
here at 51.8 on Send A Mai's
bags, 11.51 for versus cartridge's
holding was cent in seven phones and FIR
curing is very excellent, at 20 on cent, so
both FIR and promoters holding are very very  This is the
best hedge fund sold in fact it is one
percent of the holding of one percent
which is a very good thing if we
talk about its problem which process then
companies and issue other company real and good
profit growth of 23.75 versus pair
raise the price of 23.75 versus mentioning the good
thing is that the
company has been healthy dividend
payout of 21.33 but if we talk about Sainik Farms then the
stock is starting at a given first
time its book value in that if loot
and if we talk about Instagram of Great Pooja 15152
crore promoter holding economic growth then
promoter holding of Yasmin has decreased to
14.04 percent then it is
Rs.50 five
and in the graph it is absolutely stretched,
experts are saying that it is getting strong,
both MCD and signal line
are above the zero line but now they are slowly
coming down and this program is also
negative. If we talk about Mumbai or Greece
then we will discuss this topic right now  It has taken
support on the readymade, here you will see that
in the last recipe,
it has closed on the egg, if we
talk about it before this, then after Corbett, it was
showing good consolidation for the first time, that after Kuwait, it
showed the sadhu of punishment, you must be seeing that it is showing consolidation in this range,
you must be seeing that it has been
showing consolidation for a long time, one more thing is that today's two
front, it takes support on the page support near me, it has
stopped three times,
here you can see
that coming below the two medium here, it has taken
support on the support before this, it did the
same here and here also it came near 218, so
it can come near the egg, then it should take
support on the system full before that, so
if we talk about mind will, then
you should first stop and here you will see that there is
more than 130 stomach support from this thing
and 218 is at 1508, so you
can assume 3867 support or you
can take it near one and a half, you must be seeing it here, so
you  You can decide to buy somewhere in this zone.
A good
demand zone is being formed here, so a
good thing can be seen here, so you can
consider these two levels between these two.
If we talk about the target of the bank, then we
can take the target of its resistance, 1585 here you will see
135, you can take such a target,
if we talk about its last date education, then it has a
delivery of 55.07 percent,
so it is very amazing, 105 super
deliveries are good, so its
delivery of five percent is excellent, it
opened at 14814 and closed at 4047,
how did you like our video,
please tell us by commenting and if you
want fundamentals, level targets information about any other stock, then
please tell us by commenting and we will
make a video on that too, or you can ask us any question by joining the
WhatsApp group for our Telegram channel,
so you can also join our Telegram channel  You can join the
WhatsApp group,
here we have also given you our number,
that is given on Telegram but we will
give it to you in the description
and if you like our videos then
please like
and subscribe to the guide, thank you for watching
this, thank you for joining the share market which was
last by the